A Rubik's cube.
Lady Cangyue, you know what this is?
How could there be such a thing in the palace?
Eunuch Jingyuan provided the blueprint
for the young prince's new toy.
It's my first time seeing it too.
Jingyuan knows how to make modern toys.
Is he an experiencer too?
Impossible, Sister Xiaoyue.
Young Prince, you can't do this.
What are you doing?
Can I watch such R-rated plots?
Eunuch Sun.
Why do you smell
just like Auntie?
Grand Princess, Eunuch Sun.
A new clue has appeared.
Why don't I have it?
This is a reward from His Majesty.
Uh, do you want it too, Young Prince?
No, it smells bad.
I want to go play with Sister Xiaoyue.
Sister Xiaoyue, let's go.
Oh no.
I'm exposed.
The Young Prince knows.
Children say what they think.
I can explain.
If Cang Yue finds out,
His Majesty will find out.
If His Majesty finds out,
will I survive?
Cang Yue cannot be kept alive. She must die.
This palace maid must die.
But...
His Majesty likes her.
I can't let His Majesty know that I killed her.
Think of a way.
Eunuch, she's awake. She's awake.
Don't be afraid. We have nothing to hide.
Continue.
Eunuch Sun.
It seems this really is a new clue.
No matter what,
I must protect the last bloodline of the Yueyin tribe.
Your Majesty.
Didn't I tell you to call Cang Yue over?
Where is she?
Lady Cang Yue is missing.
We've searched everywhere,
but couldn't find her.
What?
However, a maid said
she saw Lady Cang Yue last go to the young prince's courtyard.
But she wasn't at the young prince's place either.
Go to Yuqing Palace.
Yes.
I got another idea.
How about poisoned wine?
Just one bowl and she'll die peacefully.
Poisoned wine?
Okay, let's use poisoned wine.
What if she's allergic to alcohol?
Get lost.
Are you allergic to alcohol?
Whatever, poisoned wine it is.
Go.
Sister Xiaoyue.
Ah.
You.
Where is Cang Yue?
Your Majesty,
she is your person.
Why would she be in Yuqing Palace?
Someone saw that
Lady Cang Yue came to
the young prince's place today.
Then I wouldn't know.
Bad news, Your Majesty!
The young prince is missing.
What did you say?
I... I know where the prince is.
Drink it.
I won't drink. I'm allergic to alcohol.
Drink!
No.
There's a sound over there.
Your Majesty.
Are you okay?
Your Highness.
Your Highness, are you okay?
Your Majesty,
I was almost beaten to death.
I don't know
how I offended Eunuch Sun
for him to be so ruthless.
Sun Liang, how dare you?
How dare you use lynching?
Your Majesty.
She clearly beat me.
Me?
Your Majesty, I'm just a weak woman.
How could I possibly beat the three of them?
Brother, I feel so dizzy.
Your Majesty.
The young prince has needle marks on him.
What?
How dare you, Sun Liang!
Not only did you plot against Cang Yue,
but you also dared to lay a hand on A Yan.
It wasn't me, Your Majesty.
It was these two young eunuchs.
I killed them for Your Majesty.
Si Xingxuan seems afraid to make a move against Eunuch Sun.
Could it be...
Eunuch Sun, why do you have
the same scent as Auntie?
Is Eunuch Sun working for the Grand Princess?